[
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "The tropics are the region of the Earth near to the equator and betw<in> the Tropic of Cancer in the northern hemis<in> and the Tropic of Capricorn in the sout<in> hemisphere. This region is also ref<in> to as the trop<in> zone and the torrid zo<in>. This area incl<in> all the ar<in> of the Earth where the sun rea<in> a point directly over<in> at least once a ye<in>. The word Tropical specifically means places near the equator.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["een", "phere", "hern", "erred", "ical", "ne", "udes", "eas", "ches", "head", "ar"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Philosophy is the study of underlying things. This means philo<in> tries to under<in> the reasons or ba<in> for things. It also tries to under<in> how things sho<in> be. A person who does philosophy is called a philo<in>. A philosopher is a thinker or rese<in>. A 'philosophy' can also mean a gr<in> of id<in> by philo<in>. Philosophy is a way of thinking about the wo<in> and soc<in>. In the pa<in>, sciences were part of philosophy.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["sophy", "stand", "sis", "stand", "uld", "sopher", "archer", "oup", "eas", "sophers", "rld", "iety", "st"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A vaccination is a treatment that makes the body stronger against an infection. The bo<in> fights infec<in> using the imm<in> system, which is made up of millions upon mill<in> of ce<in>. An important pa<in> of the immune sys<in> is that it is much stronger when fighting a disease that it has already fought aga<in> before. Vaccination invo<in> showing the immune system something which looks very similar to a parti<in> virus or bact<in>, which helps the immune system be stronger when it is fighting against the real infection.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["dy", "tions", "une", "ions", "lls", "rt", "tem", "inst", "lves", "cular", "eria"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Inflation means that the general level of prices is going up, the oppo<in> of deflation. More money will be needed to be paid for go<in> and serv<in>. Economists mea<in> inflation regu<in> to under<in> an economy's st<in>. Inflation al<in> the ra<in> of money for goods or services; more mo<in> is nee<in> to get the same amo<in> of a good or service, or the same amount of money will get a lo<in> amount of a good or service.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["site", "ods", "ices", "sure", "larly", "stand", "ate", "ters", "tio", "ney", "ded", "unt", "wer"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "The saguaro cactus is one of the defining plants of the Sonoran Desert. These pla<in> are large, tree-like columnar cacti that develop bran<in> (or arms) as they a<in>, although some ne<in> grow arms. These arms generally bend upw<in> and can num<in> over 25. Saguaros are cov<in> with prote<in> spines, white flo<in> in the late spring, a<in> red fruit in sum<in>. Saguaros are found exclusively in the Sonoran Desert.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["nts", "ches", "ge", "ver", "ard", "ber", "ered", "ctive", "wers", "nd", "mer"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Veganism is a philosophy that says people should not use animals. Vegans av<in> food that comes from ani<in>, including meat, eggs and dairy prod<in>. A vegan di<in> is sometimes called a str<in> vegetarian diet. Many vegans t<in> not to use any other ani<in> products, such as leather, wo<in>, feathers, bone, or pearl. They also try to avoid buy<in> and using products that have been tes<in> on ani<in>. They may believe in animal welfare and animal rights and may campaign for these causes.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["oid", "mals", "ucts", "et", "ict", "ry", "mal", "ol", "ing", "ted", "mals"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Superman is a famous comic book character. He is poss<in> the first mod<in> superhero character. Superman's pow<in> come from the fa<in> that he grew up on ano<in> planet, Krypton. It is sa<in> that Krypton had hig<in> gravity than Earth making the inhab<in> stronger. The Superman sym<in> and name has bec<in> a part of American cul<in> and can be seen throu<in> the culture incl<in> in songs, as nicknames, in common sayings, and more.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ibly", "ern", "ers", "ct", "ther", "id", "her", "itants", "bol", "ome", "ture", "ghout", "uding"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Albert Einstein was born in 1879 in Germany. He gr<in> to be one of the most fam<in> and brilliant scien<in> ever to have lived. Even as a young boy, Einstein sho<in> he had a great mi<in> for maths and phy<in>. During his life<in>, Albert Einstein came up with some ama<in> theories about light, matter, gra<in>, space, and time and soon enj<in> world-wide fa<in>! On April 18 1955, Albert Einstein died at the age of 76.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ew", "ous", "tists", "wed", "nd", "sics", "time", "zing", "vity", "oyed", "me"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Most schools are pretty strict about plagiarism. If you're ca<in>, you can wind up susp<in> or worse. At the very le<in>, you're prob<in> going to fail the assig<in>. When you're in col<in>, some schools will ex<in> students who plagi<in>. When you're kic<in> out of o<in> college, it can be hard to get into another.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ught", "ended", "ast", "ably", "nment", "lege", "pel", "arize", "ked", "ne"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "What is the sugar tax? Since la<in> year, the mak<in> of soft dri<in> have had to p<in> more tax under new ru<in> about the amo<in> of sugar that go<in> into their prod<in>. The new ru<in> say that each liter of sugary dr<in> would have an extra tax cha<in>, depending on h<in> much su<in> is in the drink. The move is hoped to help cut childhood obesity, tooth decay, and illnesses like diabetes.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["st", "ers", "nks", "ay", "les", "unt", "es", "ucts", "les", "ink", "rge", "ow", "gar"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Not all online content can be trusted. When us<in> the internet, it is important to under<in> the threats that may oc<in>. Technology is rap<in> evolving and as a res<in>, the way that crim<in> are using the internet is also chan<in>. There are a num<in> of different thr<in> to computer systems that inc<in>: social engineering, malicious co<in>, hu<in> error. Any risk posed to a computer system from an internet source is considered a cyber threat.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ing", "stand", "cur", "idly", "ult", "inals", "ging", "ber", "eats", "lude", "de", "man"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Musical theater is a kind of performance in a theater. A wo<in> of musical the<in> is called a musical. It us<in> acting, music, so<in>, and often da<in>. Some musi<in> have only a few lines of dia<in>. Everything else is su<in>. It is usually a mix<in> of spea<in> and song. Music has been a part of dr<in> since ancient ti<in>, but modern Western musical theatre emerged during the 19th century.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["rk", "ater", "es", "ngs", "nce", "cals", "logue", "ng", "ture", "king", "ama", "mes"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "When Abraham Lincoln first took office in 1861, the United States was not truly united. The nat<in> had been arg<in> for more than a hun<in> years about ensl<in> people and ea<in> state's right to al<in> it. Now Northerners and South<in> were cl<in> to war. When he bec<in> president, Lincoln all<in> the enslavement of peo<in> to continue in southern sta<in> but he outl<in> its spread to other exis<in> states and states that might later join the Union.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ion", "uing", "dred", "aving", "ch", "low", "erners", "ose", "ame", "owed", "ple", "tes", "awed", "ting"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "In many places around the world, children have to go to school for a certain number of years. Learning may ta<in> place in the class<in>, in outside envir<in> or on vis<in> to other pla<in>. Colleges and unive<in> are pla<in> to learn for stud<in> over 17 or 18. Vocational schools te<in> skills peo<in> need for jo<in>. Some people att<in> school lon<in> than oth<in>. This is because some jobs require more training than others.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ke", "room", "onments", "its", "ces", "rsities", "ces", "ents", "ach", "ple", "bs", "end", "ger", "ers"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Sewage is the liquid waste produced by us all when using the toilet, having a bath or sho<in>, or was<in> clothes and dis<in>. In some pla<in>, it also incl<in> rain-water fal<in> on hou<in> and roads. In big towns and cit<in>, it can also have liq<in> waste from fact<in> in it. It flows in pi<in> called se<in> to be cle<in> up at a sewage trea<in> works. Sewage is mostly water but it also has many microbes some of which can be harmful.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["wer", "hing", "hes", "ces", "udes", "ling", "ses", "ies", "uid", "ories", "pes", "wers", "aned", "tment"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Originally, the word skyscraper meant a tall sail on a sailing ship. Over ti<in>, the word's mea<in> has cha<in>, and today it me<in> a tall buil<in>. Until the nineteenth cen<in>, buil<in> taller than six sto<in> tall were not com<in>. Tall buildings ma<in> of weak mate<in> would fall do<in>. In addition, peo<in> did not like wal<in> up many steps and running water could only be brought up to fifty feet high.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["me", "ning", "nged", "ans", "ding", "tury", "dings", "ries", "mon", "de", "rials", "wn", "ple", "king"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "English is the current lingua franca of international business, science, and technology. The ri<in> of English in dipl<in> began in 1919, af<in> World War One, wh<in> the Treaty of Versailles was wri<in> in English as we<in> as in French. The u<in> of English prof<in> from the important inter<in> role of English- speaking nat<in> after World War II, parti<in> in the estab<in> and organ<in> of the United Nations. English is one of the six official languages of the United Nations.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["se", "omacy", "ter", "en", "tten", "ll", "se", "ited", "national", "ions", "cularly", "lishment", "ization"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A cheetah's spots cover nearly its entire body and may se<in> as camouflage b<in> offsetting sha<in> in the gray-hued grasses they inh<in>. Camouflage is not only esse<in> for stalking pr<in> but also for prote<in> cheetah cubs from pred<in>. Did y<in> know? Much li<in> a human finge<in>, a cheetah's spots and the ring pattern of its tail are unique!",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["rve", "y", "dows", "abit", "ntial", "ey", "cting", "ators", "ou", "ke", "rprint"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Found in northeast Africa, the Nile has long been recognized as the longest river in the world. However, there i<in> some de<in> over this ti<in>. Some scientists ar<in> that the Amazon river i<in> South America is lon<in>. The Nile h<in> been an important sou<in> of life for people throu<in> history. Around 5,000 ye<in> ago, the Ancient Egyptians rel<in> on the Nile for fr<in> water, food and trans<in>. It also provided them with fertile land to farm on.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["s", "bate", "tle", "gue", "n", "ger", "as", "rce", "ghout", "ars", "ied", "esh", "portation"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Globalization is a topic many people debate nowadays. It is the w<in> that local or nati<in> ways of doing things become glo<in>, that is, done together aro<in> the world. It is about econ<in> or trade, technology, politics, and cul<in>. It desc<in> the way coun<in> and people of the world inte<in> and integrate. People feel differ<in> about globa<in>; some think it helps everyone while others think it hurts some people.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ay", "onal", "bal", "und", "omics", "ture", "ribes", "tries", "ract", "ently", "lization"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "An earthquake is shaking of the surface of earth, caused by sudden movement in the Earth's crust. They can be extremely vio<in>. Earthquakes are usually quite br<in>, but may rep<in>. They are the res<in> of a sudden release of ene<in> in the Earth's crust. This cre<in> seismic wa<in>, which are waves of energy that travel thr<in> the Earth. The st<in> of earthquakes is cal<in> seismology. Seismology stu<in> the frequency, type and size of earthquakes over a period of time.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["lent", "ief", "eat", "ult", "rgy", "ates", "ves", "ough", "udy", "led", "dies"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A family is a group of people who, in most cases, live together. They sh<in> their money and fo<in> and are supposed to take care of one ano<in>. Its mem<in> are either genetically rel<in>, for instance, bro<in> and sisters, or legally bo<in> to each other, for example by marr<in>. In many cult<in>, the members of a fam<in> have the sa<in> or a similar sur<in>. A family is said to be society's smallest unit, its nucleus.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["are", "od", "ther", "bers", "ated", "thers", "und", "iage", "ures", "ily", "me", "name"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "People find diamonds where volcanoes were a long time ago. They some<in> find tiny ones at the si<in> of a meteorite str<in>. Sometimes people fi<in> diamonds on the t<in> of the gro<in>. But in pla<in> like South Africa, they must d<in> deep down in<in> a diamond mi<in> to get diam<in>. Diamonds were first found in India.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["times", "te", "ike", "nd", "op", "und", "ces", "ig", "to", "ne", "onds"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Even in the stone age people made music. The fi<in> music was probably ma<in> trying to imitate sounds and rhy<in> that occurred naturally. Hu<in> music may ec<in> these phenomena using patt<in> and repetition. This ki<in> of music is still here to<in>. Many peo<in> still imi<in> sounds th<in> are heard in nat<in>. Nowadays, music mostly serves as entertainment.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["rst", "de", "thms", "man", "ho", "erns", "nd", "day", "ple", "tate", "at", "ure"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Starbucks started in Seattle in the United States in 1971. The num<in> of stores has grown qui<in>. There are [ov<in>] 9,000 Starbucks stores a<in> over the wo<in>. Most of these sto<in> are in the United States. Some la<in> cities in the U.S. have ma<in> Starbucks stores. Sometimes they op<in> so many stores in one ci<in> that there are two Starbucks within a few blocks of each other.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ber", "ckly", "er", "ll", "rld", "res", "rge", "ny", "en", "ty"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Coffee is a plant and the name of the drink that is made from this plant. The cof<in> plant is a bush or tr<in> that can gr<in> up to ten meters (about 32 feet) tall, but is usu<in> cut sho<in>. Coffee plants origi<in> grew in Africa, and now also gr<in> in South America, Central America a<in> Southeast Asia. They are an impo<in> crop for the economies of many countries.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["fee", "ee", "ow", "ally", "rter", "nally", "ow", "nd", "rtant"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Animation is a way of making a movie from many still images. The ima<in> are put together one af<in> another, and then pla<in> at a fast speed to give the illusion of move<in>. Animation is a relat<in> new art form, a<in> though the con<in> of moving ima<in> has been a theme throughout ancient civilizations, it was not un<in> late into the 19th cen<in> that experimental anim<in> truly began. Today, the industry of animation is booming, making up a huge commercial enterprise.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ges", "ter", "yed", "ment", "ively", "nd", "cept", "ges", "til", "tury", "ation"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Flags can be unifying to a country, and many times are. A cou<in> that can lo<in> to its flag fly<in> high in the sky in ti<in> of tro<in> and remember that the cou<in> will go on. People that have ne<in> met before can feel un<in> towards one another kno<in> that they're pa<in> of the same country and fly the same flag.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ntry", "ok", "ing", "mes", "uble", "ntry", "ver", "ity", "wing", "rt"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Political globalization is how institutions and countries can influence the whole world. The United Nations i<in> an example of globa<in> because most coun<in> of the world are mem<in> of its General Assembly. This international organ<in> can make countries fol<in> rules and apply econ<in> sanctions to a country th<in> doesn't. This means the coun<in> in the U.N will pun<in> them by not talking or tra<in> with them so they don't benefit from globalization.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["s", "lization", "tries", "bers", "ization", "low", "omic", "at", "tries", "ish", "ding"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Our mission is to be a university that has global significance, to b<in> a lea<in> in higher educ<in> providing excellent res<in> and teaching, and contr<in> to the most impo<in> issues and deb<in> of mod<in> times. We are pro<in> that this unive<in> is increasingly having an impact worldwide.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["e", "der", "ation", "earch", "ibuting", "rtant", "ates", "ern", "ud", "rsity"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Many papers you write in college will require you to include quotes from one or mo<in> sources. Even if y<in> don't ha<in> to do it, inte<in> a few quotes in<in> your wri<in> can add life a<in> persuasiveness to your argu<in>. The k<in> is to use qu<in> to support a po<in> you're trying to make rather than just include them to fill space.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["re", "ou", "ve", "grating", "to", "ting", "nd", "ments", "ey", "otes", "int"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Road bicycle racing is the cycle sports discipline of road cycling, held on paved roads. Road racing i<in> the most pop<in> professional fo<in> of bicycle rac<in>, in te<in> of numbers of compe<in>, events, and spect<in>. The most common compe<in> format is the mass start event, where riders start simul<in> and race to set finish point.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["s", "ular", "rm", "ing", "rms", "titors", "ators", "tition", "taneously"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A young man from a small provincial town, without independent wealth, a powerful family conne<in> or a unive<in> education mo<in> to London in the la<in> 1580's and, in a remar<in> short amount of ti<in>, became the grea<in> playwright not on<in> of his age b<in> of all ti<in>. How did Shakespeare become Shakespeare?",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ctions", "rsity", "ved", "te", "kably", "me", "test", "ly", "ut", "me"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A tsunami is a natural disaster that occurs when series of waves in the ocean crash into land. A tsu<in> has a very lo<in> wavelength. It can be hundreds of kilom<in> long. Usually, a tsunami starts sudd<in>. The waves tra<in> at a great sp<in> across an oc<in> with little energy lo<in>. They can rem<in> sand from bea<in> and des<in> trees, houses and even whole towns.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["nami", "ng", "eters", "enly", "vel", "eed", "ean", "ss", "ove", "ches", "troy"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Charts are a great way to show a large amount of data. They can repr<in> numbers, words, measurements, or observations in a w<in> that ma<in> them easier to under<in> and analyze. It is impo<in> to make sure that the da<in> on your chart is pres<in> clearly and can be under<in> by any<in> who looks at it. They shouldn't have to ask you to exp<in> it.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["esent", "ay", "kes", "stand", "rtant", "ta", "ented", "stood", "one", "lain"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "The global computer network called the internet is part of our everyday lives at home. It is ma<in> up of millions of comp<in> all over the wo<in> that are digi<in> connected to each other b<in> cable, fibre o<in> wireless links. You can u<in> the internet to bro<in> websites, commu<in> with people, down<in> pictures and videos, listen to music, or do lots of ot<in> amazing things.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["de", "uters", "rld", "tally", "y", "r", "se", "wse", "nicate", "load", "her"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Computational thinking involves looking at a problem and working out a way a comp<in> might be ab<in> to help you so<in> it. To do this, you need to under<in> how a computer processes infor<in>. You probably u<in> computational thin<in> at school or wo<in> too, but don't rea<in> it. If you ana<in> a problem and plan out the solu<in>, you are using computational thinking.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["uter", "le", "lve", "stand", "mation", "se", "king", "rk", "lize", "lyze", "tions"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A programmer or software engineer is someone who designs and makes computer programs. They might u<in> one type of computer lang<in> or many. Programmers are log<in> thinkers and problem-solvers. They look at prob<in> and try to come u<in> with diff<in> ways of sol<in> them. There is often mo<in> than one w<in> to solve a pro<in> and programmers try to find the most eff<in> way.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["se", "uage", "ical", "lems", "p", "erent", "ving", "re", "ay", "blem", "icient"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Astronomy is one of the oldest sciences. Ancient peo<in> used the posi<in> of the stars to navi<in>, and to fi<in> when was the be<in> time to pla<in> crops. Astronomy is ve<in> similar t<in> astrophysics. A rel<in> subject, cosmology, i<in> concerned with stud<in> the Universe as a wh<in>, and the w<in> the universe cha<in> over time. Astronomy is n<in> the same a<in> astrology, the be<in> that motion of the st<in> and the planets may af<in> human lives.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ple", "tions", "gate", "nd", "st", "nt", "ry", "o", "ated", "s", "ying", "ole", "ay", "nged", "ot", "s", "lief", "ars", "fect"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Not everyone celebrates birthdays, including Jehovah's Witnesses. In m<in> English-speaking coun<in>, people si<in> the song 'Happy Birthday to You' to the person celeb<in> her or his birt<in>. There a<in> similar songs in ot<in> languages. A birthday ca<in> is usually deco<in> and covered with can<in>. Most of the ti<in>, the num<in> of candles is the sa<in> as the age of the birthday person.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["any", "tries", "ng", "rating", "hday", "re", "her", "ke","rated", "dles", "me", "ber", "me"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "A carpenter is a person who works with wood. They c<in> make cabinets, bu<in> houses, or do ot<in> things with wo<in>. Carpenters usu<in> make very go<in> foremen on larger jobs as they de<in> with so much of the pro<in> from ground up. Carpenters a<in> always ad<in> to their tools a<in> always lear<in> how to u<in> the n<in> tools, materials, and ways of working with wood.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["an", "ild", "her", "od", "ally", "od", "al", "ject", "re", "ding", "nd", "ning", "se", "ew"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Type the missing letters to complete the text below",
        "description": "Donald Trump was the 45th and current President of the United States. Before beco<in> president, h<in> was a busin<in> and television perso<in>. Trump w<in> the chairman and pres<in> of The Trump Organization. Much of his mo<in> was made in re<in> estate in New York City, Las Vegas, a<in> Atlantic City. He us<in> to own t<in> Miss Universe pageant. He w<in> the st<in> in his own rea<in> show The Apprentice.",
        "type": "multi-input",
        "correctAnswer": ["ming", "e", "essman", "nality", "as", "ident", "ney", "al","nd", "ed", "he", "as", "ar", "lity"],
        "madeBy": "Sanaul Haque"
    }
    
]